[MUSIC]
[背景音乐] 翻译: RyukaSuu |审阅: 19waa Coursera Global Translator Community
So now that we have created these helper functions,
现在我们已经创建了这些辅助函数
let's do this for another image here.
一起来用在这里的另外一张图片上
This is one that I cheated a little bit, I found a car, and
这是一张有点作弊的图片 我找到了一辆车 而且
then we'll just try a few examples.
之后我们会尝试一些例子
So we found a car and this car is image train and its the eighth image.
我们找到一辆在image_train中的汽车 它是第8张
So, I just went image by image to find the car.
所以我按图片顺序查找到了那辆车
And then, just so that you can see let's take the car image,
这样你就回看到 让我们看看这张汽车图片
car image dot show and we'll see the actual car we're talking about.
用car_image.show 我们就会看到实际要找的图片
And this is a red car.
这就是那张红色的车
You see it right here, red car.
你会在这里看到红色的车
The question is who are the nearest neighbours for that car.
问题在于 哪些是那辆车的最近邻
And that was this command that we did over here,
要用的是我们之前创建的命令
get_images_from_ids where we query the car.
get_images_from_ids可以查询那辆车
But I am gonna kinda shortcut things a little bit.
但我想走点捷径
So I'm going to say get_images_from_ids,
所以我想用get_images_from_ids
where I'm going to take my knn_model and
我要用knn_model且
give it as input, the car image.
把汽车图片作为输入
So knn_model, I'm going to query that current image
所以通过knn_model 我要查询当前的图片
and the output is going to be a list, an s frame, and
输出应该是个列表 一个SFrame 而且
then I'm going to select the image column of the s frame and
之后我要选择SFrame里代表图片的那一列
I'm gonna type .show in it.
在此敲入.show
And now, after I do this, you see the input car was this red car, and
现在 在此之后 你会发现输入应该是这个红色车辆 而且
now we have a bunch of red cars as near as eight.
现在我们有一些与8号汽车车相似的红色汽车
So this is really cool.
这真的很酷
In a few lines we built an example of nearest neighbors for a car and for a cat.
只需要几行 我们就建立了一个关于一辆车和一只猫的最近邻模型的例子
[MUSIC]
[背景音乐] 翻译: RyukaSuu |审阅: 19waa Coursera Global Translator Community